[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Lily] Don't let your hatred
cloud your principles.
Killing other people won't give you
the justice that you want.
[Diego] I'm not the same
Diego Torillo you knew.
And I'll never be that man again.
Now, I've realized
that the world is a cruel place,
and principles have no place in it.
And if you're going to stop me,
then best we go our separate ways.
Those pests who were
protecting Diego are now dead.
And Lily Cruz now knows that
Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
[man] All the witnesses from
Camia Cruz's camp have backed out.
[Georgina] We have to secure an advantage
before Julio's camp does.
[Lily] And the evidence
against Red Dragon?
All evidences are admissible in court.
We need a…
Credible witness.
[Lily] Tell me everything you know
that could serve as evidence
against Red Dragon.
[Myla] Now that Red Dragon
knows you know her identity,
she can take everything away from us.
[Lily] If I don't get to her first.
[Raul] I'll uncover your
mother's secrets eventually.
But for now, my son needs me.
[Lily] In every letter and every detail,
I study my enemy.
In turn, their strength
becomes mine as well.
Such is the art of war.
[Diego] I'm looking for Sanggano.
[Raul] Why? What do
you want with Sanggano?
[Diego] I'm going to kill him.
[Jose] Can you? You don't have the guts!
[grunts]
[gunshot]
Lily.
Jepoy.
I've got news.
Sanggano was found dead.
What?!
[Camia] Where?
At a beer house near town.
Lily.
Someone informed me
that the person who killed
Sanggano was Diego himself.
[dramatic music playing]
Diego?
He would never do such a thing.
[dramatic music continues playing]
That idiot!
[glass breaking]
To call Colonel Sanggano "stupid"…
would be an insult to stupid people!
Of all ways to die,
he chose a truly pathetic one,
if he had a choice at all!
How am I going to move
without a right-hand man?
And you're like a bunch
of stupid headless chickens
without your leader.
But, Governor, Sanggano's
killer wasn't just anybody.
Oh really? Humor me.
Who? Who's the wise guy
who killed Sanggano?
Tell me!
Diego Torillo.
[ominous music playing]
[scoffs]
That…
now that's definitely news to me.
Diego Torillo?
A man with a clean conscience
is capable of committing murder?
Diego Torillo committing murder.
This is unbelievable.
[chuckles]
You should be on your guard,
Governor. You could be next.
Don't be silly, boy.
As if I'd put my tail between my legs.
Hey.
I'd rather die laughing than
fear someone like Diego Torillo.
Too many people have tried to kill me.
I'm not scared of a newbie like him.
Diego Torillo?
Oh, Raul. Have you heard
what happened to Sanggano?
He died!
And guess who killed him!
It's your own bastard son, Diego Torillo!
I didn't expect that he could do it,
but I guess, he had it in him.
You know, Emilia, anyone who's
been pushed to a corner…
can do the impossible.
Wow! Really? Coming from you?
Wow, I can't believe it.
But you know,
I feel the same way now because
I feel so blind-sided by Mama
and her witch of an assistant.
And you really think my son's experience
compares to all
the pointless things you do?
[sighing]
You're unbelievable, Emilia.
[somber music playing]
Now I'm unbelievable?
[engine running]
According to the news,
Sanggano was last seen here.
Diego could be in the area.
Okay, I'll look around.
I'll come with you, Miss Camia.
Thanks, Jepoy.
[dramatic piano music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[wood breaking]
[ominous sound playing]
[dramatic music continues]
Mom.
Lily. Did you find him?
[somber piano music playing]
Let's check Mrs. Loring's house.
He's not there, Mom.
But even if he doesn't show up,
I know he's around here.
Lily, don't give up on him.
Come on, Diego.
Everyone came here to find you.
Everyone's worried about you.
Come with us.
I'm not coming with you.
Are you nuts, Diego?
Julio Ardiente will have you
killed for killing Sanggano!
You know that, right?
I'm not afraid to die.
You know what?
I really do want to join you
because I want to retaliate
with force and violence.
But you stopped me back then
because you knew it was wrong!
Just come with us!
And you once told me
that we can't take down
the Ardientes the right way,
but with force.
And now that I've gone down that path,
I can't come with you
because you'll get involved.
And if you really care
about Lily and the others,
you won't say a word about this.
[tense music playing]
Diego…
[door opens]
[door closes]
Have you found Diego?
Not yet.
I'm sorry it took me a while to come home.
I heard what happened to Diego…
and about your meeting with Red Dragon.
Damian.
You told me you know what
kind of criminal Red Dragon is.
Are you sure you don't know
her real identity?
That she's Helena Montoya?
[slow tense music playing]
Lily, I hope you can forgive me.
I only wanted to protect you.
Most especially you, Camia.
Damian, you've been living in our house.
With me and Lily.
You witnessed what my daughter
had to go through
just to discover
Red Dragon's real identity.
But you still didn't tell us the truth.
[slow tense piano music playing]
Mercedes came to see me here.
She threatened to kill the two
of you if I told you the truth.
And because I was able
to get close to Red Dragon,
I was able to find a way to protect Diego
when he infiltrated her camp
disguised as Jaguar.
[Camia] But you can't change
the fact that you betrayed us.
Damian, you should've told us the truth.
You shouldn't have lied to us.
We would have understood you.
Camia.
Thank you for protecting us, Damian…
but you betrayed me.
-Mom.
-Damian, you hurt me!
[tense piano music continues]
Thank you for… trying to protect us,
but for now,
I think you should…
I understand.
I'm leaving.
[door closes]
I just thought you should know,
that Attorney Fisher
set an appointment with me.
It looks like she's asking for a favor.
[laughing]
Well, at least they're
learning how to play.
But then again,
I'm not in the mood to play with them.
They're way too serious.
They have no sense of humor.
[laughing]
This is what I want you to do, Judge.
Shut out Lily Cruz
and that Attorney Fisher.
Too bad about that lawyer.
I find her really pretty.
-That's true.
-And sexy.
And in return for your troubles,
I give you this.
[suspenseful music playing]
[laughs]
In that case, there's nothing
left to talk about.
I knew I was right about you.
You are a man of action.
Of course. Thank you. Thank you.
Have it.
How's your mom doing?
She's upset.
She feels really betrayed.
[somber piano music playing]
Lily.
I need to tell you something.
Please don't get upset with me.
What is it?
I saw Diego earlier.
I wasn't planning on telling you,
but you might get upset with me
if you discover the truth.
He isn't ready to come back.
Lily…
I understand.
But I know he's coming back.
And I won't grow tired…
of waiting for him to come back, Jepoy.
[ominous music playing]
[paper rustling]
-[thuds]
-Whoa!
What the--?!
Get out and check it out!
[tense music playing]
Governor.
What is that?!
I'M COMING AFTER YOU NEXT!
[tense music playing]
[music intensifies]
Look.
Look at your bastard son's handiwork.
He'll always be a pest.
[laughing]
[Julio chuckles]
Well, Emilia--
It's good to know you're amused.
I just remember those times you laughed
at my hallucinations of Lily Cruz.
Now it's happening to you!
[laughing]
Your fear over Diego Torillo is legit.
Shut up!
Raul,
your son's horns are showing.
And if you don't talk to him,
I'll break off those horns myself.
He's a different man now, Papa.
My son has forgotten he was ever
a part of this family.
He's forgotten
that you were ever his Grandpa.
What if I forget that you're my husband?
Now you have to choose
between Diego or the Ardientes.
Choose.
[tense music playing]
[scoffs]
Cat got your tongue again.
I don't care about your husband, Emilia.
All that matters is that
we stick together as a family.
The blood coursing through
our veins is pure Ardiente.
And I don't want the blood of my
grandson to be associated with
and tainted by
that peasant vigilante, Diego.
[tense music continues]
[tense music playing]
[inaudible]
-[gunshot]
-[screams]
-[breathing heavily]
-[tense music playing]
[Emilia] My son!
How are you?
Come here. Come here. Oh, my baby boy.
You're so thin and you're so…
dark.
Good grief, that's it, okay?
You're coming home.
-Jenny, get his room ready.
-There's no need.
-I just want to talk to my grandfather.
-Okay.
Arnaldo, even with bodyguards,
that hut doesn't suit you.
Listen to me. You are an Ardiente.
You are meant for greater things.
You should come home
instead of acting all nice.
I mean, look at you.
You heard the man, Emilia.
Leave my grandson to me.
We have a lot to talk about.
Okay. Bye.
[sighing]
You should come home soon.
[slow tense music playing]
[birds chirping]
Make sure you do everything as instructed,
especially concerning the documents.
Yes, ma'am.
Another package came in for you.
[ominous sound]
[tense music continues]
Madam's messages have been
getting more frequent.
I consulted her on a few matters.
Leave.
[Mercedes] If you know yourself,
but not the enemy,
for every victory gained,
you will also suffer defeat.
Know your enemy.
Fool them, and act in ways
they will never suspect.
Only then will you achieve true victory.
[tense music continues]
[Mercedes] Deliver the documents
to Red Dragon.
But deliver them to the address
written below,
not to the first one mentioned,
so that the enemy cannot track them.
You've always been smart at
doing the unpredictable, Madam.
As you wish.
[tense music playing]
Would you like to join me?
Grandpa, I think we should pray
for Colonel Sanggano's soul.
Arnaldo.
I'm not disrespecting you,
but can that wait?
There's something more important
you should know.
The identity of Sanggano's killer.
It was none other
than your wonderful brother,
Diego Torillo.
He's the one who killed Sanggano.
You know, a lot of people
think I'm bad. That I'm evil.
But what they don't know is,
between me and Diego,
he's way more of a criminal
than I've ever been.
I don't believe what you're saying.
Diego's such a kind person.
He wouldn't do that.
His kind is nothing
but a bunch of murderers!
I'm not mad at you, Arnaldo.
I'm just stressing the fact.
I'm your grandfather.
[in English] I'm your grandfather.
I'm the only one who you can trust.
Because I only have your welfare in mind.
Nothing else.
All I want is whatever
will be good for you.
So please, I'm begging you.
Leave that ratty house
and those fields and come home.
Live where a proper prince
like you should live.
Stay here, in our palace.
I already told you I'm not coming home,
and that hasn't changed.
[sighs]
I came because I have
a lot of questions, and…
I think you might be able to answer them.
I have a lot to ask about…
about Lily.
And if you can answer them--
You'll come back.
[tense music playing]
You see?
I'm right.
You have it in you. It's natural.
It's natural for an Ardiente
to be a great negotiator.
Okay? You'll come back.
Do we have a deal?
I will answer all your questions.
But you have to come back home.
[music intensifies]
That's my grandson.
[tense music continues]
[suspenseful music playing]
Red Dragon wants to see me privately.
So, you two stay here.
Madam, here are your files.
[suspenseful music continues]
[music swells]
[in Chinese] Hello, Mercedes.
You?!
Yes, Mercedes. It's me.
[tense music playing]
[Lily] If you know yourself
but not the enemy,
for every victory gained,
you will also suffer a defeat.
[henchwoman] Mercedes, this came in.
It's just how I am.
I make sure I know my enemies well.
From the head down to the toes.
So that I can camouflage as the enemy.
Where's Red Dragon?
Mm… [laughing]
I don't know where she is.
But if you still don't get it, Mercedes,
I was the one sending you letters.
[tense music playing]
[in Chinese] Thank you, Mercedes.
-[grunts]
-[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[thuds]
[tense music continues]
[people screaming]
So, Mercedes, tell me,
what's the passcode?
There is no passcode.
Mercedes, you had the vault prepared.
Remember?
[Mercedes] Sahara.
Yes, Madam Mercedes.
Prepare the vault.
[Sahara] Yes, Madam.
[suspenseful music playing]
Aren't you an expert in hacking?
Just like what you did to my laptop?
Go ahead. Have a field day
finding the key to the vault.
-Enjoy!
-No!
This conversation won't be over
until you tell me the passcode!
[people screaming]
[tense action music playing]
[whooshing]
[grunting]
[thuds]
[tense action music continues]
[grunts]
[grunting continuously]
[Lily coughing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunting]
[action music playing]
[thuds]
So… You still won't give me
the passcode, huh?
No!
I would rather die than
give Lily Cruz what she wants.
Okay. Looks like you really mean it.
So, I'll give you that.
Besides, the evidence I got
is more than enough.
[grunts]
[Mercedes grunting]
[in Chinese] Thank you, Mercedes.
[in Chinese] I won.
[tense music playing]
To start off,
here is a big answer
to one of your questions.
[tense music intensifies]
[Arnaldo] We were married?
[Julio] You were supposed to be,
but it was a big trap
to humiliate our whole family
to the entire town.
Truth is, you were their main target.
They wanted to humiliate you.
They hurt you and totally
destroyed your dignity.
And everything was planned
by none other than that woman,
Lily Cruz, whom you used to know
as Ivy Aguas.
And she didn't do it by herself.
She got help from your brother Diego.
They planned to bring you down
and crush our entire family.
Yes, it's true.
You got that woman first,
but Diego took her from you.
That's how sly your brother is.
Lily Cruz lied to you, and so did Diego.
Those two ganged up on you.
They were conniving all along.
Now, you see how vile they are?
[tense music playing]
They are evil!
[citizens yelling]
Stop! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Everyone, calm down.
Thanks for helping me out.
I appreciate that you're checking on me.
Thank you so much.
You're really kind, Diego.
[somber piano music playing]
[crying]
Arnaldo.
Arnaldo, my boy.
[crying]
Relax.
I know it's a lot to take in.
Relax, relax. You're home.
You're home. Jenny!
Jenny, get me a glass of water!
Relax. Relax, my boy. Relax.
Relax.
I'm here. I'm here.
I'll take care of you.
You're home. You're home.
[somber piano music continues]
I'm about to reclaim my office, Arnaldo.
An office which you will inherit.
That's why you need to come back.
Come back so we can take Diego down.
[ominous music playing]
You have to come back.
I'll put a stop to your plans,
Julio Ardiente.
My brother will stand by my side and I…
I will be the governor of Ardiente.
Me! Not you!
[gunshot]
[ominous music continues]
[gasping]
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
You have no right to invade
my sanity, Diego.
I'll be the one to end you.
[exhales sharply]
The evidence is strong.
Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
But… there's something missing.
What, Attorney?
Bank accounts that will prove
how big their operation is.
Then we will need a list
of Red Dragon's present clients.
Lists, bank accounts,
whatever you need, I'll find it.
I'll get it from them, Attorney.
[tense music playing]
We will expose Red Dragon.
And we will put a stop
to all her operations.
[suspenseful music playing]
Does Red Dragon know?
[door closes]
Yes, and she's not happy, Mercedes.
I need to do something.
Red Dragon knows that Diego
killed Colonel Sanggano
and that Julio Ardiente can't
sleep at night because of it.
And?
Red Dragon wants to recruit
Diego Torillo into the group.
[dramatic music playing]
Colonel Magbanua.
I do hope that you'll prove
to be a lot more competent
than that good-for-nothing
Colonel Sanggano.
Now,
your first mission as my right-hand man
is to hunt down Diego Torillo.
I don't know how that man is still alive.
That Diego Torillo can pray if he wants,
but that won't save him from me.
Brilliant.
Now then,
Judge Lustre,
where were we?
This is not good.
You can't have a death threat
while we're preparing your reinstatement.
I'm just worried you might be distracted.
Judge, a push-over like
Diego Torillo can't scare me.
Mark my words, the moment
I reclaim my throne,
Diego Torillo, Helena Montoya, Lily Cruz…
I'll throw their heads in the dumpster.
Mark my words.
[tense music playing]
Diego Torillo?
Why him?
Not even Emilia could join us.
What help can Diego Torillo
possibly offer?
[suspenseful music playing]
Mercedes.
I'll use Diego Torillo
against Julio, obviously.
But the most
important thing is that
this is the perfect venue
to get revenge on Lily Cruz.
For what she did to my daughter,
for stealing those files,
and for trying to infiltrate
in our organization.
There's nothing more painful
than trying to see
your loved one enter the enemy zone.
And while we're corrupting Diego Torillo,
it will only make it worse for Lily Cruz.
And once he's really corrupted,
that's when we'll kill him
because he'll know too much.
And don't think of asking where I am.
Listen closely, Mercedes.
This is your last chance
to redeem yourself.
Recruit Diego Torillo
or die!
[tense music playing]
[birds chirping]
[suspenseful music playing]
I got your message.
What do you want from me?
For a fugitive,
you're not difficult to find.
But then again,
what reason do you need
if you really want something?
Red Dragon extends you her invitation
to join our organization.
You will be paid handsomely.
And you wouldn't have to hide
from the people hunting you
for Sanggano's death.
You'll also get revenge on Julio Ardiente
for killing your foster parents.
If there's anyone
who can defeat Julio Ardiente,
it's definitely Red Dragon.
[Mercedes] I can go on and on.
But we don't have all day.
What do you say?
[gunshot]
[Diego] I promise you this,
Julio Ardiente,
You'll pay for what you did
to my foster parents!
I'll bring you down!
[Lily] If you could only see yourself…
It's like you're ready to kill!
And I won't let you do that!
I won't let you turn into a criminal!
There's no place for justice
here in Ardiente!
I will kill them.
Diego!
[gunshot]
[suspenseful music playing]
I accept.
But not so I can be your pet.
[tense music playing]
You know what I'm capable of.
So, what do you propose?
I won't join your group as an underling.
I want to join as Red Dragon's ally.
Her ally?
[Helena] Diego Torillo.
What can you bring to the table
to prove you deserve to be my ally?
Hmm…
[tense music continues]
If you decline,
then I won't force you.
[mobile phone ringing]
Yes, Madam?
Mercedes.
Diego!
[tense music playing]
Welcome to the organization
as Red Dragon's ally.
What?! Diego Torillo?
That Diego Torillo
was made an ally?
-Does Mama know?
-Yes, Madam.
The order came from Red Dragon herself.
This is unbelievable.
And it's all Mercedes' fault.
She got pissed off
when I stormed into
your office the other day,
and now this happens.
Okay.
I want you to continue
spying for me over there.
I'll wire you money.
[Raul] Diego?
They're recruiting Diego to
become Emilia's mother's ally?
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
Hello, Mama. Come on, pick up the phone.
How can you not consider my feelings
in getting that Diego Torillo?!
You know how much I hate that guy!
Pick up the--
[grunts]
[sighs]
That Diego Torillo
doesn't deserve to be
an ally of Red Dragon!
[Raul] So, Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
[suspenseful music playing]
[line ringing]
[door closes]
Who are you?
The name's Colonel Magbanua.
Is Diego Torillo here?
We're here to arrest him
for murdering our comrade,
Colonel Sanggano.
You're one of Julio Ardiente's henchmen?
Then tell your boss that Diego isn't here.
[Lily] Mom?
What's going on here?
Good evening! Good evening, Lily Cruz.
I'd like you to know
that all your bodyguards are…
being held at gunpoint by my men.
It's just you and your mother now.
Two women, plus your nincompoop
driver at the back.
Meanwhile, I have 10 of my men here,
so I think it'd be better
if you just let us inside.
One more step, Julio Ardiente,
and you'll regret it.
[tense music playing]
[Julio laughing]
Lily, let's not waste time here.
Surrender Diego Torillo to me
and I will leave
your premises peacefully, okay?
-[Julio] Come on.
-Okay.
-[gunshot]
-[Julio] Whoa!
[Julio] Look!
What was that for, Lily?!
You almost hit my foot!
Have you gone deaf, old man?
I said if you take one
more step, you'll regret it.
Diego Torillo isn't here.
And when I say something, I mean it.
As for you…
We haven't been introduced
but now you'll know who I am.
I am Lily Cruz.
And if you stand in my way,
you'll be sorry!
[tense music playing]
This is crazy! We outnumber them.
Come on!
[rapid gunfire]
Whoa! Stop it!
[Lily] Now…
-Whoa!
-If you insist on entering.
[gun cocks]
-[Julio] Whoa!
-[tense music playing]
Just walk this way, Julio Ardiente.
I won't think twice
about blowing your brains out.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Arnaldo] I can't take it anymore!
Lily. Take me to Lily.
I need to talk to her.
[chuckles] Ivy.
[Diego] I'm here for my mission,
to bring down the Ardientes.
[Romulo] I hope Red Dragon
was right to recruit you.
[Julio] Even if you band
together with all my enemies,
you are not going to shake me down.
Bring me Diego Torillo. The war has begun.
[Helena] I want you to kill Lily Cruz.
[suspenseful music playing]
[theme music playing]